## **ABOUT ME**

Ambitious and driven professional with expert knowledge client Dealing in the Service Industries. Strong interpersonal skills, a friendly and approachable disposition together with hone psychological and interpersonal skills lends to a position where rapid reading of situations and subsequent reaction is required. A self-starter can work efficiently on own initiative or can integrate easily into a team environment.

#### LANGUAGES

HINDI

**GUJARATI** 

**ENGLISH** 

# FALGUNI GOSWAMI

**BACK OFFICE EXECUTIVE** 



+917048789330



falguni.goswami1994@gmail.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **AEGIS LTD**

AHMEDABAD May 2013 - Jun 2014

#### Customer care executive

( Successfully served as a Customer care executive from May 2013 to June 2014 eg. 1 year) KEY ACHIEVEMENTS: - Customer query solving Customer Satisfaction Solve Network Issue in Outbound Department Time to Time Updating and Training Review documents Provide enough information to Customer

#### JUST DIAL LTD

AHMEDABAD Jul 2014 - Jan 2016

### ■ Tele - Marketing

(Satisfactorily served as a Tele – Marketing from July 2014 to January 2016 ) KEY ACHIEVEMENTS: -

- -Email Coding-Decoding
- -Data maintaining
- -Calling to given data
- -Target achiever
- -Solve complains
- -To provide solutions to different Problems
- -Maintain strong relationships with clients
- -Rewarded by many certificates related extra ordinary works and dedication.

# MI SERVICE CENTER

AHMEDABAD Sep 2017 - Feb 2021

#### Tele caller Cum Front desk Executive

Workes As Telecaller, Feedback , Backoffice, Admin work and into the Documentation work

Maintained detailed product knowledge to competently and expertly advise customers.

Made high volume of sales calls per day exceeding company outbound call targets.

Handled and quickly resolved customer issues regarding product sales and customer service problems.

Dealt with complex customer complaints professionally and politely, resolving issues with favourable solutions.

## VIVO SERVICE CENTER

AHMEDABAD Mar 2021 - Present

#### BACK OFFICE Executive

Customer Handing

Tele calling on given data

Maintain Customer feedback

Data Operating & Data submission in system

Maintain good Repo with clients

Healthy interaction with customers

Complains Resolution

Involve in administrative work

Organise training schedules

Current Package- 20000/-

Expected Package- 26,000 /-

**DECLARATION:** 

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned particulars are true & correct to the best of my knowledge and belief

# **EDUCATION**

GUJARAT UNIVERSITY 2020



c	v	ш	ı c
3	n	IL	L9

SALES CUSTOMER SATISFACTION

COMMUNICATIONS